Maxwell Bruce

+61 406 030 344

MaxwellWallaceBruce@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/mwbruce github.com/MWBruce

About

I am a First-Class Honors Computer Science and Commerce graduate from the University of Adelaide. This resume encapsulates my key experiences, awards and skills, yet for a more comprehensive insight and about my professional path, I invite you to visit my professional webpage designed and developed by me at https://mwbruce.github.io/#.

Education (GPA 6.5/7.0)

Bachelor of Computer Science (First Class Honors) The University of Adelaide (Graduated November 2024)

Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting and Corporate

The University of Adelaide (Graduated November 2024)

Awards

Adelaide Summer Research Scholarship	2023/2024
The Software Engineering Prize	2023
Innovative Software Engineering Award	2024

Experience

SAAB Australia

Software and Machine Learning Engineer – 0.75 FTE 11/2023 - Present

- Developed and integrated various models using Python and C++ to analyse and model defence systems.
- Utilised various machine learning algorithms including and not limited to Generative Adversarial Networks, Diffusion Models, Convolutional Neural Networks, Transformers and LSTMs.

Australian Institute for Machine Learning

Machine Learning Researcher - 0.2 FTE 04/2023 - Present

- Developed machine learning algorithms under Dr Jinan Zuo allowing me to develop a foundation of machine learning knowledge.
- I am currently writing a paper about an algorithm developed by me which enhanced a trading models' ability to generalize to unseen market environments.

RJC Evans & Co Pty Ltd

Accountant 04/2020 - 04/2023

Community Engagement

Competitive Programming Club

Treasurer (Volunteer)

11/2023 - 11/2024

- Compete in various competitive programming competitions in a team of three.
- Manage the club's financial responsibilities, including cashflows.

AI Camp (A Start Up)

Co-Founder

10/2024 - Present

- Develop and oversee the development team for supporting AI Camp software in development.
- Organize and arrange for school visits introducing machine learning as a teaching tool for teachers and advertising software products.
- Manage staff and oversee business finances.

Projects

HTML/CSS

• URL:

https://github.com/MWBruce/MWBruce.githu b.io (Or web link https://mwbruce.github.io/#).

Description: My professional website outlining all up-to-date projects I am doing and relevant information about me.

TypeScript

https://github.com/MWBruce/Zettlr

Description: My open-source contribution to the Zettlr fixing a feature relating to how references were managed internally.

C++

URL:

https://github.com/MWBruce/FinancialModeli ngPrepWrapper

Description: Developing a wrapper for a popular stock data API to collect users requested data.

Languages

C++, Python, HTML, Java, SQL, JavaScript, CSS, C, TypeScript.